

SEBASTIAN MARCELO STAROPOLI

ELECTRONIC TECHNICIAN

SUMMARY

I am an electronic technician with expierence using measurement tools. Experienced in electronic materials and repearing electronic circuit boards. Basic knowledge in programming languages such as C, C++, .NET. Advanced knowledge using HTML5 and CSS

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- Creative
- Innovatibe
- Serviced Focused
- Complex problem solver
- Easy going
- Drive license B1

CONTACT

Phone: 4915732623154

Email: datahola22@gmail.com

Adress: Zoppoter Strabe 8, Dusseldorf

Alemania

LANGUAJES

- English
- Spanish

CERTIFICATES

- English: Cambridge Institute Certificate graduated in 2018
- Ides Institute: Computer mechanic and webs
- CoderHouse: Web Developer

EXPERIENCE

Libson Group SRL

MECHANIC FROM JANUARY 2021 TO NOVEMBER 2021

- Repearing electrical appliances
- Packaging
- Sales

Electro Chance SRL

MECHANIC FROM AUGUST 2018 TO JANUARY 2021

- Production of electronic roulettes
- Production of electronic machinery
- Repearing electronic circuit boards

SC Instalaciones

FROM DECEMBER 2021 TO JUNE 2022

- Assambling of electromechanical equipment

Living Hotel De Medici

FROM JUNE 2022

- HouseKeeping
- -Public Area

EDUCATION

Technical School Number 6

ELECTRONIC TECHNICIAN

- Graduated in 2017

National University of La Matanza

INFORMATIC ENGINEERING

- Still in progress